Your memaw died?
(Sheldon:)That's terrible.
(Wil Wheaton:)Yeah. It was.
(Wil Wheaton:)But I'm really sorry
that I disappointed you.
(Sheldon:)No, no, I understand.
If anything happened to my memaw,
I'd be one inconsolable Moon Pie.
(Sheldon:)I should clarify that statement
by explaining that she calls me Moon Pie.
It's a special relationship, isn't it?
Between a boy and his grandmother.
(Sheldon:)-Oh, yes.
RAJESH: Yeah, okay.
(Raj:)Okay, great,
everybody loves their grandmas.
(Raj:)Now, come on, Sheldon,
finish him off.
Yeah. It's okay, Sheldon.
I let you down.
(Wil Wheaton:)I deserve it.
(Sheldon:)Potion of Zancor.
(Raj:)What are you waiting for?
(Raj:)Kill Wil Wheaton.
From hell's heart, stab at him.
(Leonard:)-I can't.
-Sure you can. Do it. Do it.
(Penny:)No.